A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992., Extent: 45.15 cubic feet (129 boxes). (Box 1-129)
  - Public Library files, 1920-1971.
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1959. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1958-1959. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1958. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1954-1957. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1950-1953. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1953-1957. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1948-1952. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1946-1947. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1945. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1944. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Loudoun County Public Library (See also Purcellville Public Library), 1934-1943. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Louisa County, 1953-1971. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Louisa County, 1954. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Louisa County, 1953. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Louisa County, 1953. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Louisa County, 1945-1952. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Lunenburg County - See Southside Regional Library, 1943-1971.
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1968-1971. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1967. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1967. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1966. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1966 June-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1966 Jan-May. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1965. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Lynchburg Public Library (See also Jones Memorial Library), 1954-1964. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Lynchburg Public Library - Miller Park Library, 1941-1948. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lynchburg Public Library - Negro Library, 1948-1950. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1968-1971. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1962-1967. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1960-1961. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1958-1959. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1956-1957. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1955. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1953-1954. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1951-1952. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1948-1950. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - McIntire Public Library (Albemarle County and Charlottesville), 1945-1947. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Madison County Library, 1941-1971. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library (See also Henry County), 1969-1971. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library (See also Henry County), 1966-1968. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library (See also Henry County), 1961-1965. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library (See also Henry County), 1951-1960. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library (See also Henry County), 1946-1950. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mathews County Public Library, 1966-1971. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Mathews County Public Library, 1956-1965. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mathews County Public Library, 1951-1955. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mathews County Public Library, 1947-1950. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mathews County Public Library, 1944-1946. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1966-1971. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1965-1965. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1956-1963. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1956-1963. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1950-1955. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library (Hopewell), 1941-1949. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Mecklenburg County - See Southside Regional Library, 1943-1971.
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1970-1971. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1962-2969. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1956-1961. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1953-1955. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1951-1952. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1948-1950. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Montgomery-Radford Regional Library, 1941-1947. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 1965-1970. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 1956-1964. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 1950-1955. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 19. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Nansemond County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library), 1941-1971.
    - Narrows Public Library (See also Giles County), 1957-1970. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - New Market, 1964. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1970-1971. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1969. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1968. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1961-1967. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Newport News Public Library - Clippings (See also Warwick Library), 1957-1968. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Newport News Public Library - Photographs (See also Warwick Library), 1964-1965. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1955-1960. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Newport News Public Library (See also Warwick Library), 1941-1954. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1966-1969. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1960-1965. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1954-1959. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1951-1953. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1948-1950. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1945-1947. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - (South) Norfolk Public Library, 1943-1963. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Northampton County - See Eastern Shore Public Library, 1941-1971.
    - Northumberland Memorial Library - See also The Community Library, 1956-1971. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Nottoway County Public Library, 1962-1971. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Nottoway County Public Library, 1948-1954. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Nottoway County Public Library, 1941-1947. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1966-1971. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1961-1965. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1955-1960. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1954. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1952-1953. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1949-1951. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1948. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1946-1947. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1941-1945. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1962-1970. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1959-1961. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1953-1955. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1951-1952. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1949-1950. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1947-1948. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library (Caroline, Hanover, King William), 1941-1946. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Patrick Henry Memorial Library - See also Campbell County Public Library, 1958-1970. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Patrick Henry Memorial Library - See also Campbell County Public Library, 1951-1957. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Patrick Henry Memorial Library - See also Campbell County Public Library, 1941-1950. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1967-1971. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1965-1967. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1962-1964. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1967-1971. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1956-1966. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1926-1929; 1940-1955. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1964-1971. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1956-1963. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1945-1955. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1968-1971. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1964-1967. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1955-1963. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Powhatan County Public Library, 1941-1958. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Prince Edward County - See also Farmville Public Library, 1953-1958; 1965; 1970-1971. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Prince Edward County - See also Farmville Public Library, 1949-1952. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Prince Edward County - See also Farmville Public Library, 1947-1948. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Prince Edward County - See also Farmville Public Library, 1945-1946. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1968-1971. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1967. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1965-1966. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1961-1964. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1958-1960. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1956-1958. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1954-1955. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1953. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1953. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1952. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1941-1952. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Princess Anne County - See Virginia Beach Public Library, 1941-1971.
    - Pulaski County Library, 1965-1971. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1962-1964. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1957-1961. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1954-1956. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1949-1953. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Pukaski County Library, 1947-1948. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1945-1946. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Purcellville Public Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1968-1971. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Purcellville Public Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1965-1967. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Purcellville Public Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1960-1964. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Purcellville Public Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1956-1959. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Radford Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1946-1971. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1968-1971. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1964-1967. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1956-1963. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1920-1955. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1966-1968. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1963-1965. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1960-1962. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1956-1959. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1951-1955. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1946-1950. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1941-1945. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1962-1964. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1960-1961. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1956-1959. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1955. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1954. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1953. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1951. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1950. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1949. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1948. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1945-1947. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1960-1964. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1956-1959. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1954-1955. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1952-1953. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1950-1952. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1948-1949. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1947. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1946. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Rockingham County Public Library, 1942-1945. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1966-1971. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1962-1965. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1961. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1960. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1950-1959. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Salem Public Library, 1940-1971. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Samuels Public Library (Front Royal), 1958-1971. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Shenandoah County - See Edinburg Community Library, 1969-1971.
    - Smithfield - See Benjamin P. Chapman Memorial Library, 1959-1971.
    - Smyth County Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Smyth County Public Library, 1950-1964. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Smyth County Public Library, 1947-1949. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Smyth County Public Library, 1945-1946. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Southampton County - See also Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1942-1955. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Southside Regional Library (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg), 1960-1971. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Southside Regional Library (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg), 1954-1959. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Southside Regional Library (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg), 1949-1953. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Southside Regional Library (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg), 1947-1948. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Southside Regional Library (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg), 1943-1946. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Spotsylvania County - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1945-1971.
    - Stafford County, 1945-1971. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1966-1970. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1956-1965. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1950-1955. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1945-1949. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Strasburg Community Library, 1965-1971. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Strasburg Community Library, 1961-1964. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Strasburg Community Library, 1958-1960. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Surry County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1941-1971.
    - Sussex County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1941-1971.
    - Suffolk - See Morgan Memorial Library, 1945-1970.
    - Tazewell County Library, 1968-1971. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1967. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1966. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1966. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1965. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1964. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1964. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Tazewell County Library, 1946-1963. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Balch Library (Leesburg), 1963-1970. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Urbanna Public Library, 1958-1971. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1968. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1967. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1964-1966. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Beach - Princess Anne Public Library, 1960-1963. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Beach - Princess Anne Public Library, 1956-1959. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Beach - Princess Anne Public Library, 1941-1950. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Wallace Library - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1945-1971.
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin, Isle of Wight, Nansemond, Southampton, Surry, Sussex), 1968-1971. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin, Isle of Wight, Nansemond, Southampton, Surry, Sussex), 1964-1967. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin, Isle of Wight, Nansemond, Southampton, Surry, Sussex), 1961-1963. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin, Isle of Wight, Nansemond, Southampton, Surry, Sussex), 1958-1960. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin, Isle of Wight, Nansemond, Southampton, Surry, Sussex), 1955-1957. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Franklin Library Association), 1956-1971. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Isle of Wight), 1941-1949. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Surry), 1945-1959. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library (Sussex), 1946-1961. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Warren County Public Library - See also Samuels Public Library, 1941-1958. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Warrenton Public Library - See Fauquier Public Library, 1957-1968.
    - Warwick Library - See also Newport News Public Library, 1953-1956. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Warwick Library - See also Newport News Public Library, 1945-1952. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1968-1970. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1966-1967. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1962-1965. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1961-1962. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1960. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1959. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1957-1958. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1956. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1956. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1954. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1954. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1951-1953. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1949-1950. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1947-1948. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1946. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1940-1945. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1967-1969. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1966. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1961-1965. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1951-1960. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1945-1950. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Westmoreland County - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library and Henry Hungerford Library, 1945-1971.
    - Williamsburg Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Williamsburg Public Library, 1966-1968. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Williamsburg Public Library, 1960-1965. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Williamsburg Public Library, 1941-1959. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Winchester - See Handley Library, 1945-1970.
    - Wise County - See Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1946-1971.
    - Wytheville Public Library, 1960-1970. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1969-1971. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1964-1968. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1961-1963. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1958-1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1954-1957. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1951-1953. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1949-1950. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1948. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1937-1947. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - York County Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Public Library files, 1971-1986.
    This sub-series consists of 32 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by the name of the public library or by the locality if no public library exists, and in reverse chronological order thereunder.
    - Accomac County - See Eastern Shore Public Library
    - Albemarle County - See Jefferson-Madison Regional Library
    - Alexandria Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Alexandria Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Alleghany County - See Charles P. Jones Memorial Library
    - Altavista Public Library (See also Campbell County), 1975-1984. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Amelia County Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1977-1980. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Appomattox Regional Library, 1981-1985. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox Regional Library, 1971-1980. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Arlington County Library, 1981-1985. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Arlington County Library, 1977-1980. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County Library, 1971-1976. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Augusta County Library, 1981-1985. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Augusta County Library, 1975-1980. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Bath County, 1971-1976. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Bedford Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Bedford Public Library, 1978-1981. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Bedford Public Library, 1971-1977. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Benjamin P. Chapman Memorial Library, 1972-1973. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1978-1981. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1975-1977. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Botetourt County Library, 1982-1985. (Box 52, Folder 2)